All will be forgiven... all but one
The Rapture is a mystery, drama, fantasy film directed by Michael Tolkin.
A lonely telephone operator leading an empty, amoral life finds God – only to have her
faith continually tested in ways beyond what she could have imagined.
Sharon, played by Mimi Rogers.
Randy, played by David Duchovny.
Vic, played by Patrick Bauchau.
Mary, played by Kimberly Cullum.
Deputy Foster, played by Will Patton.
Paula, played by Terri Hanauer.
The Rapture is a 1991 drama film written and directed by Michael Tolkin.
It stars Mimi Rogers as a woman who converts from a swinger to a born-again
Christian after learning that a true Rapture is upon the world.
The low-budget film was a box office disappointment while critical reception was generally
positive, with Rogers' performance praised as perhaps the best of her career.
The film explores themes of faith, religion and
supernatural, eroticism, group sex, bible.
The tone is intense and lighthearted and emotional.